听力考试正式开始。
请看听力部分第一。
节。
第一节，听下面五段对话，
每段对话后有一个小题。
从题中所给的
三个选项中，选出最佳选项，并。
标在试卷的相应位置。
听完每段对话后，你都有十秒钟的时间
来回答有关小题和阅读下一小题。
每段对话仅读一遍。
例如，现在你有五秒钟的时间看试卷上的例题。
你将听到以下内容：“
你将有五秒钟的时间，将正确答案
标在试卷上。
衬衫的价格为九磅十五便士，
所以。
你选择
项，并将其标在试卷上。
现在，你有五秒钟的时间
阅读第一小题的有关内容
Who will join us for dinner tonight?
Bob and Candy.
I also invited Mary, but she is out of town.
What a pity!
I was hoping she would come.
If I were you, I'd just walk to work.
It would take you about twenty minutes.
Riding a bike is a good choice too.
I agree. But this week my husband is away on business, so I have to drive my kids to
school before I go to work.
I'm pressed for time, you
It's eight thirty, Dave, and you're going to be late for the meeting.
Oh my! I just have half an hour left.
I can't believe I slept for ten hours!
Hi Helen, where are you off to?
To the library.
I've got a history paper due next week and need to do some reading.
Thank goodness you are still here!
What's up? I need your signature for this document.
It's urgent. the B,
第一节到此结束。
第二节，听下面。
五段对话或独白，每段对话或独白后
有几个小题，从题中所给的
三个选项中，选出最佳选项，并标在试卷的相应位置。
听每段对话或独白前，
你将有时间阅读各个小题。
每小题五秒钟。
听完后，各小题将给出五秒钟的作答时间。
每段对话或独白，读两遍。
听下面一段对话，回答
reading. questions.
第六和第七两个小题。
现在你有十秒钟的时间
阅读。
这两个小题。
Are you all alone, Tom?
Why not ask Mike to help you collect money for the Children's Center?
Well, he's working on his lab report.
Could you come?
I'd love to, but I won't be available until next week.
I think Kathy will have some free time this week.
Do you want me to pass on a message?
That'd be nice.
Thanks, Jane. Are you all alone, Tom?
Why not ask Mike to help you collect money for the Children's Center?
Well, he's working on his lab report.
Could you come?
I'd love to, but I won't be available until next week.
I think Kathy will have some free time this week.
Do want me to pass on a That'd be nice.
Thanks, Jane. Listen
听下面一段对话，回答
第八至第十三个小。
题。
现在你有十五秒钟的时间
阅读这三个小题。
questions. avoiding the rush hour traffic.
I don't want to be late.
So you have to wait for about two hours?
I don't think there's scenery to look at.
Don't worry. I'll take a book with me.
It's too noisy to read in the railway station.
I would usually look around the shops while waiting for the train.
But I've already got all the gifts for my parents and sisters.
I don't need to buy anything.
If I really can't focus on the book, I may phone up some friends I haven't talked to
in a while.
That's a nice idea.
Betty told me last time that she often spent the waiting time writing a to -do list
so that she'd not miss anything in the days to come.
That's an awesome idea.
I'll surely do that.
Thank you, Judy.
See you next year.
Bye. Are you leaving for the railway station now, Jack?
It's so early.
Just avoiding the rush hour traffic.
I don't want to be late.
So you have to wait for about two hours?
I don't think there's scenery to look at.
Don't worry. I'll take a book with me.
It's too noisy to read in the railway station.
I would usually look around the shops while waiting for the train.
I don't think there's look I don't think to at.
I don't think scenery look scenery look I don't look
look I don't I don't think look
I look I don't there's don't
听下面一段对话，回答
第十一至第十三三个小题。
现在，你有十五秒钟的时间
阅读这三个小题。
I don't think look I don't think look My uncle offered me a job as the lead engineer
at his service station and with good pay.
That's wonderful. But are you going to quit college?
That's exactly the problem.
One side of me says, oh, go ahead.
You can go back to college any time.
What job could you get after college that would pay you fifteen dollars an hour?
That's thirty thousand dollars a year.
And then? And then the other side says, hold it.
Not so fast.
For all those years you were in the army, you planned to go to college so that you
would have many job possibilities to choose from.
You've planned your whole life around going to college, and now...
I can see it.
It's true that with your experience in the army, you could do excellent work
repairing cars if you accept the job.
But you are doing very well now.
Just think of the future.
You will get better jobs.
Hi, Bill. You look troubled.
What's the matter?
Hi, Grace. I have a big decision to make.
My uncle offered me a job as the lead engineer at his service station and with good
pay. That's wonderful.
But are you going to quit college?
That's exactly the problem.
One side of me says, oh, go ahead.
You can go back to college any time.
What job could you get after college that would pay you fifteen dollars an hour?
That's thirty thousand dollars a year.
And then? And then the other side says, hold it.
Not so fast.
For all those years you were in the army, you planned to go to college so that you
would have many job possibilities to choose from.
You've planned your whole life around going to college, and now...
I can see it.
It's true that with your experience in the army, you could do excellent work
repairing cars if you accept the job.
But you are doing very well now.
Just think of the future.
You will get better jobs.
听下面一段对话，回答
第十四至第十六。
三个小题。
现在你有十五秒钟的时间
阅读这三个小题。
Hey, John, can I talk to you for a minute?
Sure. What's up?
I wanted to let you know about a book club I joined a few months ago.
I know you do a lot of reading, so I thought you might want to come with me next
month. Oh, that sounds like fun.
When does the group meet?
Usually the last Saturday of the month at 7.30 in the evening.
Is that too late for you?
No, I think that's okay.
What do you talk about in the group?
Well, every month we choose a new book, and then during the next meeting we discuss
it. What books have you read?
Quite a lot.
Recently we have read The Beautiful Mind and The Great Gatsby.
Now we are reading The Kite Runner.
The Kite Runner?
I've heard that's a good book.
What's it about?
It's about a boy who grows up in Afghanistan during the 1980s.
That sounds interesting.
I'd love to come.
Great. The next meeting will be held in two weeks, so you still have time to read
the book. Hey, John, can I talk to you for a minute?
Sure. What's up?
I wanted to let you know about a book club I joined a few months ago.
I know you do a lot of reading, so I thought you might want to come with me next
month. Oh, that sounds like fun.
When does the group meet?
Usually the last Saturday of the month at 7.30 in the evening.
Is that too late for you?
No, I think that's okay.
What do you talk about in the group?
Well, every month we choose a new book, and then during the next meeting we discuss
it. What books have you read?
Quite a lot.
Recently we have read The Beautiful Mind and The Great Gatsby.
Now we are reading The Kite Runner.
The Kite Runner?
I've heard that's a good book.
What's it about?
It's about a boy who grows up in Afghanistan during the 1980s.
That sounds interesting.
I'd love to come.
Great. The next meeting will be held in two weeks, so you still have time to read
the book. Today let's begin with note -taking techniques.
听下面一段独白，回答
第十七至第二十四个小题。
现。
现在，你有二十秒钟的时间
阅读这四个小题。
Note -taking is an important skill not only for taking classes, but also for doing
your job in the future.
I'd like to draw your attention to certain points about taking notes.
First, remember that note -taking should be 75 listening and only 25 writing.
So don't try to write down every single word the teacher says.
Ignore what is unimportant and write in phrases, not complete sentences.
Second, leave spaces and lines between main ideas.
You may want to add some information later.
I find that some of you are very good at making use of color, mapping web, and
symbols such as arrows, circles, and boxes.
I highly recommend these tools to all of you because the use of them makes the
outline more easily readable and interesting than the blocks of text.
It also makes sure that important words stand out.
Here are some examples.
Today let's begin with note -taking techniques.
Note -taking is an important skill not only for taking classes, but also for doing
your job in the future.
I'd like to draw your attention to certain points about taking notes.
First, remember that note -taking should be 75 listening and only 25 writing.
So don't try to write down every single word the teacher says.
Ignore what is unimportant and write in phrases, not complete sentences.
Second, leave spaces and lines between main ideas.
You may want to add some information later.
I find that some of you are very good at making use of mapping web, and symbols such
as circles, and boxes.
I highly recommend these tools to all of you because the use of them makes the
outline more easily readable and interesting than the blocks of text.
It also makes sure that important words stand out.
Here are some examples.
The you. Thank you.
第二节到此结束。
现在，你有两分钟的时间，将试卷上的答案
转涂到答题卡上。
Thank you. Thank you.
听力部分到此结束。